

#### **PERSONAL DATA**

- NAME SZYMON MOZOL
- ADDRESS KLEVE, HOFFMANNALLEE
- PHONE NUMBER +48 512 743 315
- EMAIL
  SZYMONMOZOL123@GMAIL.COM
- in LINKEDIN

#### **WEBSITES**



**MYSITE** 



**GITHUB** 



ITCH.IO



**NEWGROUNDS** 



**FIVERR** 



**YOUTUBE** 

### **SKILLS**

- C#
- UNITY ENGINE
- GIT
- CODE OPTIMIZATION
- DESIGN PRINCIPLES
- DESIGN PATTERNS
- ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES
- JIRA

### **LANGUAGES**

POLISH (NATIVE) ENGLISH (B2) GERMAN (A1)

# SZYMON MOZOL

#### UNITY DEVELOPER/PROGRAMMER

I am a bachelor's degree holder in Computer Science at WSB Merito University in Wrocław with specialization in cloud application developer. I spend most of my time creating games in Unity Engine with emphasis on programming them. I am learning to program in C# but i also know Java and C++. I can write clean, optimal and efficient code. I know the Unity engine very well, I can use event system, animations, UI, particle system, lighting system, sound system, the new Input system, import assets and configure them, handle 2D/3D graphics and much more. Ever since my childhood, I have cultivated a deep fascination for video games. Creating, playing, immersing myself in discussions about them, and avidly watching gaming content are my primary passions.



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Mar 2024 - Jun 2024

Junior Web Developer
Weni Solutions, Nysa

IT specialist - Intern
Collins Aerospace, Wrocław

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

IT specialist
Żabka Poland

IT specialist



# **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2023

Bachelor degree WSB Merito University, Wrocław

Secondary education
Zespół Szkół i Placówek Oświatowych,

Głuchołazy

Technikum nr 2, Nysa

Specialist Hospital MSWiA in

I also obtained an IT Technician license



## **CERTIFICATE**

2023

ISTQB Certified
Tester Foundation Level

2018

Cisco IT Essentials



## PRIVACY STATEMENT

I hereby agree to processing of my personal data included in the recruitment application in the recruitment process for the position indicated in the job offer published by the company Virtual Alchemy sp. z o. o.